Black Sparrow Press Collection, 1966-1994 (bulk 1973-1993)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Book Files, 1973-1993
  - #474 The Trick, Dawson, Fielding, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - #474 The Trick, Dawson, Fielding, Artwork, 1991 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - #474 The Trick, Dawson, Fielding, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - #474 The Trick, Dawson, Fielding, Discarded Materials, 1991 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - #474 The Trick, Dawson, Fielding, First proof, 1991 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - #474 The Trick, Dawson, Fielding, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - #475 Hank, The Life Of Charles Bukowski, Cherkovski, Charles, Artwork, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - #475 Hank, The Life Of Charles Bukowski, Cherkovski, Charles, 1 Hardcover, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, Artwork, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, Manuscript (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, Manuscript (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, Manuscript (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, First proof (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, First proof (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - #476 The Season, It Was Winter, Sanford, John, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, Artwork, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, Fante/Covici letters, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, Letters from Rome, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, First proof (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, First proof (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - #477 Selected Letters: 1932-1977, Fante, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, Artwork, 1991 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, First Manuscript (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, First Manuscript (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, Final Manuscript (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, Final Manuscript (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, Discarded Materials, 1991 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - #478 Minding The Underworld, Christensen, Paul, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - #479 In The Shadow Of The Rose, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - #479 In The Shadow Of The Rose, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1991 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - #479 In The Shadow Of The Rose, Bukowski, Charles, First Manuscript, 1991 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - #479 In The Shadow Of The Rose, Bukowski, Charles, Final Manuscript, 1991 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - #479 In The Shadow Of The Rose, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover copies, 1991 (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - #480 The Revenge For Love, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - #480 The Revenge For Love, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, 1991 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - #480 The Revenge For Love, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - #480 The Revenge For Love, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - #480 The Revenge For Love, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - #481 By The Sound, Dorn, Edward, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - #481 By The Sound, Dorn, Edward, Artwork, 1991 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - #481 By The Sound, Dorn, Edward, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - #481 By The Sound, Dorn, Edward, First proof, 1991 (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - #481 By The Sound, Dorn, Edward,3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - #482 Three Diamonds, Malanga, Gerard, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - #482 Three Diamonds, Malanga, Gerard, Artwork, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - #482 Three Diamonds, Malanga, Gerard, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - #482 Three Diamonds, Malanga, Gerard, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - #483 Just Space,Kyger, Joanne, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - #483 Just Space, Kyger, Joanne, Artwork, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - #483 Just Space, Kyger, Joanne, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - #483 Just Space, Kyger, Joanne, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - #483 Just Space, Kyger, Joanne, 2 Hardcover copies, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - #484 Dream Palace, Purdy, James, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - #484 Dream Palace, Purdy, James, Artwork, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - #484 Dream Palace, Purdy, James, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - #484 Dream Palace, Purdy, James, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - #485 The Bluebird., Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, and Back Matter, 1991 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - #486 Insel, Loy, Mina, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - #486 Insel, Loy, Mina, Artwork, 1991 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - #486 Insel, Loy, Mina, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - #486 Insel, Loy, Mina, Discarded Materials (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - #486 Insel, Loy, Mina,3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 254, Folder 7)
  - #487 Bitches Ride Alone,Chester, Laura, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - #487 Bitches Ride Alone, Chester, Laura, Artwork, 1991 (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - #487 Bitches Ride Alone, Chester, Laura, First Manuscript, 1991 (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - #487 Bitches Ride Alone, Chester, Laura, Final Manuscript, 1991 (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - #487 Bitches Ride Alone, Chester, Laura, Discarded Materials, 1991 (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - #487 Bitches Ride Alone, Chester, Laura, 1 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 255, Folder 6)
  - #487 Bitches Ride Alone, Chester, Laura, 2 Hardcover Copies, 1991 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - #488 House Tours, Jaffe, Sherril, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - #488 House Tours, Jaffe, Sherril, Artwork, 1991 (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - #488 House Tours, Jaffe, Sherril, Manuscript, 1991 (Box 256, Folder 4, Folder 5)
  - #488 House Tours, Jaffe, Sherril, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1991 (Box 256)
  - #489 Now, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork and Manuscript, 1992 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - #489 Now, Bukowski, Charles, 15 signed tip-ins, 3 soft cover, 2 Hardcover, 1992 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - #490 A Brief History of Camouflage, Frank, Thaisa, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - #490 A Brief History of Camouflage, Frank, Thaisa, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - #490 A Brief History of Camouflage, Frank, Thaisa, Artwork, 1992 (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - #490 A Brief History of Camouflage, Frank, Thaisa, Manuscript, 1992 (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - #490 A Brief History of Camouflage, Frank, Thaisa, Discarded Materials (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - #490 A Brief History of Camouflage, Frank, Thaisa, Discarded Materials (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - #490 A Brief History of Camouflage,Frank, Thaisa, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - #491 The Last Night Of The Earth Poems, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1992 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - #491 The Last Night Of The Earth Poems,Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - #491 The Last Night Of The Earth Poems,Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - #491 The Last Night Of The Earth Poems, Bukowski, Charles, 4 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - #492 Sleepwalker’s Fate, Clark, Tom, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - #492 Sleepwalker’s Fate, Clark, Tom, Artwork, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - #492 Sleepwalker’s Fate, Clark, Tom, Manuscript, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - #492 Sleepwalker’s Fate, Clark, Tom, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - #493 Birds, Beasts and Flowers,Lawrence, D.H., Correspondence, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - #493 Birds, Beasts and Flowers, Lawrence, D.H., Artwork, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - #493 Birds, Beasts and Flowers, Lawrence, D.H., Manuscript, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - #493 Birds, Beasts and Flowers, Lawrence, D.H., 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - #494 Three by Bukowski, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, Back Matter and 3 Softcovers, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - #495 Looking For Genet, Chester, Alfred, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - #495 Looking For Genet, Chester, Alfred, Artwork, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - #495 Looking For Genet, Chester, Alfred, Manuscript, 1992 (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - #495 Looking For Genet, Chester, Alfred, Discarded Materials, 1992 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - #495 Looking For Genet, Chester, Alfred, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - #496 A Strange Market, Kelly, Robert, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - #496 A Strange Market, Kelly, Robert, Artwork, 1992 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - #496 A Strange Market, Kelly, Robert, Manuscript, 1992 (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - #496 A Strange Market, Kelly, Robert, 1 Hardcover copy and 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - #496 A Strange Market, Kelly, Robert, 2 Hardcover Copies, 1992 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - #497 Fulfilment And Other Tales, Boutilier, Nancy, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - #497 Fulfilment And Other Tales, Boutilier, Nancy, Artwork, 1992 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - #497 Fulfilment And Other Tales, Boutilier, Nancy,First Manuscript (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - #497 Fulfilment And Other Tales, Boutilier, Nancy, 1992 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - #497 Fulfilment And Other Tales, Boutilier, Nancy, Second Manuscript, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - #498 According To Her Contours, Boutilier, Nancy, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - #498 According To Her Contours, Boutilier, Nancy, Artwork, 1992 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - #498 According To Her Contours, Boutilier, Nancy, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - #498 According To Her Contours, Boutilier, Nancy, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - #498 According To Her Contours, Boutilier, Nancy, Discarded Materials, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - #498 According To Her Contours, Boutilier, Nancy, First Proof, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - #498 According To Her Contours, Boutilier, Nancy, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - #499 Counting Myself Lucky, Field, Edward, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - #499 Counting Myself Lucky, Field, Edward, Artwork, 1992 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - #499 Counting Myself Lucky, Field, Edward, Manuscript, 1992 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - #499 Counting Myself Lucky, Field, Edward, Discarded Materials, 1992 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - #499 Counting Myself Lucky, Field, Edward, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - #500 Edificio Sayonara, Yau, John, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - #500 Edificio Sayonara, Yau, John, Artwork, 1992 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - #500 Edificio Sayonara, Yau, John, Manuscript, 1992 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - #500 Edificio Sayonara, Yau, John, Discarded Materials, 1992 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - #500 Edificio Sayonara, Yau, John,3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1992 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - #501 Those Marvelous Lunches, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, Back Matter, 2 Softcovers, and 1 Hardcover, 1993 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - #502 Hand Dance, Coleman, Wanda, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - #502 Hand Dance, Coleman, Wanda, Artwork, 1993 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - #502 Hand Dance, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - #502 Hand Dance, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - #502 Hand Dance, Coleman, Wanda, First Corrections, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover; 1993 (Box 268, Folder 6, Folder 7)
  - #503 So Long, Berlin, Lucia, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - #503 So Long, Berlin, Lucia, Artwork, 1993 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - #503 So Long, Berlin, Lucia, Early versions, 1993 (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - #503 So Long, Berlin, Lucia, Manuscript, 1993 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - #503 So Long, Berlin, Lucia, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1993 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - #504 Jason The Sailor, Wakoski, Diane, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - #504 Jason The Sailor, Wakoski, Diane, Artwork, 1993 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - #504 Jason The Sailor, Wakoski, Diane, Manuscript, 1993 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - #504 Jason The Sailor, Wakoski, Diane, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1993 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - #505 Hymn To The Rebel Cafe, Sanders, Edward, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - #505 Hymn To The Rebel Cafe, Sanders, Edward, Artwork, 1993 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - #505 Hymn To The Rebel Cafe, Sanders, Edward, Manuscript, 1993 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - #505 Hymn To The Rebel Cafe, Sanders, Edward, Discarded Materials, 1993 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - #505 Hymn To The Rebel Cafe, Sanders, Edward, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1993 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    It is unknown what title was designated with this project number and whether a file exists for this project in the series.
  - #507 Writing My Life, Morris, Wright, Correspondence and Artwork, 1993 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - #507 Writing My Life, Morris, Wright, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - #507 Writing My Life, Morris, Wright, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - #507 Writing My Life, Morris, Wright, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1993 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, 1993 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript Index, 1993 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Back Matter: Notes to afterword, 1993 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Back Matter: 2 Canceled Chapters, and Explanatory Notes, 1993 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Back Matter: Books by Wyndham Lewis, Index, and Critical Reception, 1993 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, Back Matter: Books by Wyndham Lewis, Textual appendix, 1993 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - #508 Time And Western Man, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1993 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - #509 Way West, Dorn, Edward, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - #509 Way West, Dorn, Edward, Artwork, 1993 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - #509 Way West, Dorn, Edward, Manuscript, 1993 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - #509 Way West, Dorn, Edward, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1993 (Box 275, Folder 4)
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1971-1982
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order, according to sender, which include publishing houses, bookstores, authors, and acquaintances of John Martin. Letters are unrelated to the works listed in Series I; a few include unsolicited manuscripts, and very few examples of Martin’s responses are represented here.
  - A, 1976-1982 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Acker, Kathy, 1976-1977 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Aldebaran Review, 1977 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Don, 1977-1978 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Allen, R.G., 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Alpert, Barry, 1975-1977 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - The Alternative Press, 1977, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - Am Here Books (Richard Aaron), 1976 (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - The American Poetry Review, 1975-1976 (Box 276, Folder 9)
  - Ampersand Books, 1976-1979 (Box 276, Folder 10)
  - Andersen, Mary K., 1975-1979 (Box 276, Folder 11)
  - Andrews, Lawrence, 1980-1982 (Box 276, Folder 12)
  - Anson-Cartwright, Hugh, 1977-1982 (Box 276, Folder 13)
  - Antæus / The Echo Press, 1975-1976 (Box 276, Folder 14)
  - Antin, Davio, 1972-1977 (Box 276, Folder 15)
  - Aquila Publishing Company, 1974-1976 (Box 276, Folder 16)
  - Aquila Publishing Company, 1974-1978 (Box 276, Folder 17)
  - Arcade, The Comics Review, 1975-1977 (Box 276, Folder 18)
  - Ashbery, John, 1976-1980 (Box 276, Folder 19)
  - Auster, Paul, 1975-1976 (Box 276, Folder 20)
  - B, 1975-1982 (Box 276, Folder 21)
  - Bachy (Lawrence D. Stewart), 1975 (Box 276, Folder 22)
  - Balaban, John, 1977 (Box 276, Folder 23)
  - Baldwin, Neil, 1976, 1982 (Box 276, Folder 24)
  - Banyan Press, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 25)
  - Baranchik, Marc, 1976 (Box 276, Folder 26)
  - Bartlett, Lee, 1979-1981 (Box 276, Folder 27)
  - Bartlett, Lee, 1979-1981 (Box 276, Folder 28)
  - Bell, Joe, 1976 (Box 276, Folder 29)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1974-1975 (Box 276, Folder 30)
  - Berrigan, Daniel, 1977 (Box 276, Folder 31)
  - Bertholf, Robert, 1975-1979 (Box 276, Folder 32)
  - Betts, Glynne Robinson, 1979 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Bitchrock, 1982 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Blackburn, Joan/Paul, 1976-1979 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Blackrose Bookstore, 1982 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - Blaser, Robin, 1975, 1977 (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - Blasingame, Michael, 1975-1976 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - Blue Horse, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - The Book Bus/Visual Studies Workshop, 1977 (Box 277, Folder 8)
  - Book Center, Inc., 1978 (Box 277, Folder 9)
  - Book House Northwest, 1977 (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - The Book Organization/The Book Bus, 1974-1976 (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - Book Project (Luan Perry), 1976-1978 (Box 277, Folder 12)
  - Book (Leeds, England), 1975 (Box 277, Folder 13)
  - Bookslinger, 1979 (Box 277, Folder 14)
  - Borchardt, Georges Inc., 1981 (Box 277, Folder 15)
  - Borsten, Orin, 1974-1982 (Box 277, Folder 16)
  - Boulevards, 1980; 1974-1982 (Box 277, Folder 17)
  - Boulton, J.T., 1980 (Box 277, Folder 18)
  - Bowles, Paul, 1976-1978 (Box 277, Folder 19)
  - Bowering, George, 1976 (Box 277, Folder 20)
  - Brainard, Joe, 1971, 1975 (Box 277, Folder 21)
  - Braverman, Kate, 1979-1980 (Box 277, Folder 22)
  - Breger, Udo, 1975 (Box 277, Folder 23)
  - Brenner, Summer, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 24)
  - Bromige, David, 1968-1981 (Box 277, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Steven Ford, 1976-1977 (Box 277, Folder 26)
  - Buell, Frederick, 1978 (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - Burns, Howard, 1976 (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - Burns, Jim, 1977 (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - Butterick, George, 1979 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - Byrd, Donald J., 1978 (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - C, 1975-1982 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - Calder, John LTD (Publishers), 1981 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Carcanet New Press Limited, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 8)
  - Carter, Ray, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 9)
  - Caveman Press, 1976-1977 (Box 278, Folder 10)
  - Charters, Ann, 1979-1980 (Box 278, Folder 11)
  - Chavez, Damiana, 1975-1981 (Box 278, Folder 12)
  - Christie, Tom, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 13)
  - Clark, B. Hannetta, 1978-1980 (Box 278, Folder 14)
  - Clark, L.D., 1979 (Box 278, Folder 15)
  - Clark, Tom, 1976-1981 (Box 278, Folder 16)
  - Cohen, Allen, 1979-1981 (Box 278, Folder 17)
  - Cohen, Marvin, 1976-1977 (Box 278, Folder 18)
  - Coleman, Wanda, 1979-1982 (Box 278, Folder 19)
  - College Marketing Group, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 278, Folder 20)
  - Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers (COSMEP), 1975-1978 (Box 278, Folder 21)
  - Compendium, 1975, 1977 (Box 278, Folder 22)
  - Congdon, Kirby, 1976 (Box 278, Folder 23)
  - Congdon, Kirby, 1976 (Box 278, Folder 23)
  - Cooney, Seamus, 1975-1981 (Box 278, Folder 24)
  - Corman, Cid, 1975-1978; 1980 (Box 278, Folder 25)
  - Cowasjee, Saros, 1976-1977 (Box 278, Folder 26)
  - California Rehabilitation Center, 1981-1982 (Box 278, Folder 27)
  - Creeley, Robert, 1970; 1974-1982 (Box 278, Folder 28)
  - Crepuscular Press, 1976, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 29)
  - Crozier, Andren, 1977-1982 (Box 278, Folder 30)
  - Cullin, John, 1978 (Box 278, Folder 31)
  - Curry, Dave, 1976-1977 (Box 278, Folder 32)
  - Cushing, Thomas, 1981-1982 (Box 278, Folder 33)
  - Cushman, Keith, 1975-1982 (Box 278, Folder 34)
  - D, 1975-1982 (Box 279, Folder 1)
  - Dailey, Victoria K., 1976-1977 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Dana, Robert, 1981-1982 (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - Davidson, Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - Dawson, Fielding, 1975-1981 (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - DeLoach, Allen, 1975 (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - Dexter, Bruce, 1977 (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Dierkes, Henry, 1979 (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - Dillon, Millicent, 1980-1981 (Box 279, Folder 9)
  - Dobson, Sylvia, 1985 (Box 279, Folder 10)
  - Doubleday, 1977 (Box 279, Folder 11)
  - Douglas, Max, 1969-1972; 1977-1979 (Box 279, Folder 12)
  - Douglas, Max, (includes 3 Manuscripts, undated) (Box 279, Folder 13)
  - The Downtown Review, 1979 (Box 279, Folder 14)
  - Dragonwagon, Crescent, 1980-1982 (Box 279, Folder 15)
  - Duncan, Robert, 1971-1972 (Box 279, Folder 16)
  - E, 1975-1982 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Eddington, Patrick, 1975, 1979 (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - Edwards, Paul, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Eiges, Mark, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - The Eighth Street Bookshop, Inc., 1976; 1979 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - Eiener, Larry, 1978-1980 (Box 280, Folder 7)
  - The Elizabeth Press (James L. Weil), 1977-1978 (Box 280, Folder 8)
  - The English Agency (Japan) LTD, 1982 (Box 280, Folder 9)
  - Enslin, Theodore, 1975-1981 (Box 280, Folder 10)
  - Eshelman, Clayton Poems 6, 1969-1982 (Box 280, Folder 11)
  - Eshelman, Clayton, 1969-1982 (Box 280, Folder 12)
  - Everman, Welch D., 1975; 1977 (Box 280, Folder 13)
  - Everson, William, 1977-1981 (Box 280, Folder 14)
  - F, 1976-1982 (Box 280, Folder 15)
  - Faas, Ekbert, 1978-1982 (Box 280, Folder 16)
  - Fabian, Robert, 1978 (Box 280, Folder 17)
  - Fabricant, Andrew R., 1980-1981 (Box 280, Folder 18)
  - Fagin, Larry, 1977-1978 (Box 280, Folder 19)
  - Fante, Joyce, 1980; 1982 (Box 280, Folder 20)
  - Fee, Ian, 1982 (Box 280, Folder 21)
  - Feldman, Arthur, 1970; 1976-1982 (Box 280, Folder 22)
  - Ferrier, Carole, 1975; 1978 (Box 280, Folder 23)
  - Ferriss, Lucy, 1979-1980 (Box 280, Folder 24)
  - Finlay, Sue/Ian Hamilton, 1975-1979 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Finney, Brian H., 1971 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Fitzpatrick, Frank, 1979-1982 (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Fogel, Al, 1981-1982 (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Folmsbee, Jeff, 1982 (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Ford, Charles Henry, 1976-1982 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Ford, Hugh, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Forrest, Michael, 1979-1981 (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Fox, C. J., 1978, 1980-1982 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Fraser, Kathleen, 1976 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Frost, Everett C., 1979-1980 (Box 281, Folder 11)
  - G, 1975-1982 (Box 281, Folder 12)
  - Gangemi, Kenneth, 1976-1981 (Box 281, Folder 13)
  - Gardner, Jean, 1980 (Box 281, Folder 14)
  - Gay Sunshine, 1976, 1979 (Box 281, Folder 15)
  - Genson, V. A., 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 281, Folder 16)
  - Germain, Ed, 1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 281, Folder 17)
  - Ghiselin, Brewster, 1974 (Box 281, Folder 18)